(Sheldon:)of your subtropical girlfriend.
(Raj:)Hey! That's my sister
(Raj:)and my country
you're talking about.
(Raj:)Leonard may have
defiled one,
(Raj:)but I won't have you
talking smack about the other.
(Bernadette:)You guys ready to order?
(Sheldon:)Yes, I'd like a seven-day
course of penicillin,
(Sheldon:)some, uh, syrup of ipecac--
to induce vomiting-- and a mint.
(Bernadette:)I don't understand.
(Howard:)He drank from
Leonard's glass.
"He drank from
Leonard's glass"--
the words they'll be
carving into my tombstone.
(Leonard:)That's actually my napkin.
(Sheldon:)Oh, this is a nightmare!
(Howard:)Where are you going?
To the bar,
(Sheldon:)to sterilize my mouth
with alcohol.
(Sheldon:)Gang way! Dead man walking!
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪